# **Azandegbe Frank**

# Web Developer



I have been working in web development for over 4 years. Most of the time I have been working with the front-end area, but I like to challenge myself with tasks related to both back-end and front-end.

I have had a lot of varied experience with technologies such as Angular and vanilla JS. I have experience with WordPress and PHP as well.



# CONTACT



Ukraine Mariupol



+38 (063) 293-33-05



beninbenino@gmail.com



github.com/mrbenino



# र्ीं SKILLS

JS, Angular, TS

HTML, CSS, SCSS, LESS, Liquid (Shopify themes)

PHP, NodeJS, Kotlin

InnoDB, MySQL, Postgres

Google API, LiqPay SDK, Instagram API



# **EDUCATION**

#### IT STEP Computer Academy

• Web and Software development



#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Self employment

August 2017 - September 2018

- · Developing sites for local businesses
- · Used Java to create an API
- · Created sites on Mod-X

#### Leo CRAFT Digital

October 2018 - September 2020

- Participated in the development of the custom CMS
- Implemented connection of several Google APIs
- · Working with payment systems

# Yeda developing learning environments Ltd

December 2020 - March 2012

- Worked with Laravel
- Participated in development of the internal product for Angular

# Foresinght Trading Group LTD

March 2021 - July 2021

- Working with Wordpress
- · Creating calculators for Vue.js

#### BSX

August 2021 - to today

· Working with Angular

